

#### **Contacts**

Dnipro,Ukraine

+380974335970

rudomanovdmitrij@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/ https://github.com/

# **Tech Skills**

- HTML5
- . . . . .
- SCSS
- GIT
- JavaScript
- WebPack
- React
- Doduy
- Vue
- Node

## Soft Skills

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Decision-making
- Leadership
- Creativity
- Stress management

## **Language Skills**

- Russian : Native
- Ukrainian : Native
- English : Upper-intermediate

## **Front-End Developer**

# **Dmitrij Rudomanov**

I'm a Frontend developer with experience in building websites and APP`s. Whether you're trying to win work, list your services or even create a whole online store – I can help! I'm experienced in HTML and CSS3, SCSS, JS, React, Vue, Node. Regular communication is really important to me, so let's keep in touch!

# **Project Experience**

1.	WALLET   Project Link
	Team React-NodeJS project.Simple and usefull Wallet App
2.	PHONEBOOK   Project Link
	Solo React-Redux project.Simple user friendly Pnonebook App
3.	SHOP   Project Link
	Solo Vue project.Online shop with currency exchange
4.	FILMOTEKA   Project Link [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
	JS team project with me as Teamlead. Movie site easy to use
5.	WEBSTUDIO   Project Link
	Educational markup project. Simple and Interactive
6.	ICECREAM   Project Link
	Team project.lceCream selling web-site.Role:Developer,Code reviewer
7.	WOODER   Project Link
	Building an interesting landing website for wood furniture company
8.	OFDR   Project Link [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
	Web-site for insurance companie.
9.	FUNIRO   Project Link
	A modern web-store that sels best quality furniture
10.	LOGO   Project Link
	Website for online Sport-shop
11.	BENTLEY   Project Link [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
	Working on official Bentley web-page in Ukraine
12.	LUX-TRADER   Project Link
	Luxury Auctions Web-site with golden design.
13.	BINARY   Project Link
	Modern innovative designers web-page.
14.	PRIME-ONE   Project Link
	Web-Site for very creative foodmaking organiztion
15	RIKE I Project Link

## **Work Experience**

# **Svet-LED Company Web-site editor**

Simple but eyecatching landing page with vintage bikes.

September 2019 - January 2019 | Ukraine

- Editing the list of products on the site
- Products information update

### Restaurant 'SHO PO CHEM'

## Waiter

June 2019 - September 2019 | Ukraine

- Taking orders from visitors
- Customer service

## **Education**

### **PSACEA**

**International Economics and business** 

September 2018 - June 2023 | Ukraine

# **Additional Education**

### GOIT

## FULL STACK course online